Tell me.
Why did you need to call us here?
L-Like I said...
You and the others are blessed with Gifts,
and we wanted you all to have a wonderful time.
Is that really the reason?
I suspect it's because either
your community was weak to begin with,
or something happened that caused it to go into decline.
Your silence says it all, Black Rabbit.
I don't believe I said you could sit here, Galdo Gasper.
I'm not here to talk to you.
I want to talk to these young ladies.
Us?
Yes, that's correct.
Would you be interested in joining my community
along with Black Rabbit and the rest?
You're right, Izayoi.
Our community is in dire straits.
The "communities" I mentioned to you before
are a bit like countries, whether big or small.
So, in addition to a community's normal operations,
they must also register a formal name and banner
with the Little Garden administration.
A formal name and banner?
So a community's banner is like a country's flag?
Yes. Many use it to mark their territory.
Up until a few years ago, our banner had flown proudly
all the way to the ends of the East Side.
However, one day we ran afoul of an enemy
which we should have avoided at all costs, and then...
In just one night, we were wiped out.
Basically, this guy is a leader in name only.
A ghost from the past.
But would it really be possible to destroy
an organization that large in a single night?
There are some here for whom
that would be child's play.
They are the greatest terror
the Little Garden has ever known:
the Demon Lords.
Demon Lords?
Yes. When a Demon Lord
challenges someone to a Gift Game,
refusal is not an option.
Jin Russell's community was forced
to participate in one of those Gift Games,
and ultimately, his community was destroyed.
The Demon Lord's strength was overwhelming.
Our community lost the Gift Game,
was stripped of its name and banner,
and became the "No-Names."
A nameless community, huh?
Yes.
None of our core members remain,
and we have no one to replace them.
The only people we have
who can participate in Gift Games
are the current leader—Master Jin—and myself.
The remaining members,
almost one hundred and twenty in number,
are children aged ten or younger.
Sounds pretty dire to me.
I know, right?
Still, everyone is trying their hardest to survive.
The children fetch water from a far-off river every day.
The only land that's still fertile and capable
of supporting crops is the very land they live on.
Oh?
If the situation is that bad, why not just
disband the organization and make another?
W-We can't do that!
Why?
We... We want to protect the homes of our friends.
And someday,
we want to get our name and banner
back from the Demon Lord,
and rebuild our community.
That's why we need players
with great powers like you and the others!
Please... Please help us!
If he turns us down now, all hope is lost.
So you're trying to revive a community
while challenging a Demon Lord, huh?
Sounds good.
Huh?
Don't "huh" me. I'm gonna help you.
Turn that frown upside down.
B-But...
Going up against a Demon Lord
to reclaim one's flag and honor...
Sounds kinda cool.
A perfect reason to help you guys out.
Expect wonders, Black Rabbit.
Thank you!
I see.
So you want us to join your community instead of theirs,
as theirs has no benefits?
That's correct.
My community, Fores Garo,
has won the banners of countless
other communities through Gift Games,
and now we control this area.
I needn't even explain in detail
how our community compares
to Jin Russell and his No-Names.
So I shall ask you again, ladies.
Please join our community,
along with Black Rabbit and—
No, thank you.
Huh?
What?
I have no intention of joining your community.
I think Jin's community is a better fit.
Wh-Why?
Kasukabe, what would you like to do?
The only reason I came here was to make friends.
Oh, I see.
Then would you be so good as to
consider me candidate number one?
Sure.
How nice for you, little miss!
I'm so happy you found a human friend.
Could you please tell me
how you came to such a decision?
You see, I, Kudou Asuka,
left behind my possessions, my family name,
my guaranteed future—all of it—
and came to this world.
Did you really believe that I would be happy
to enter into a privileged environment once again?
But—
Be quiet.
You know, there is one thing I'm curious about.
Sit down and answer my questions.
Jin...
Y-Yes?
Do communities often end up
staking their name and banner in such games?
Not if they can help it.
Those bets are basically equivalent
to betting your community itself.
I thought as much.
That's why these Demon Lords are so feared.
And you're not a Demon Lord,
so how were you able to pull off all of these victories?
Tell me.
We would kidnap the enemy's women and children,
and use them to threaten their community
into participating in our game.
Well, that's quite savage.
So I assume that's why all of
the communities you've absorbed
work under you so obediently.
We've taken several children from each
community hostage to ensure that.
So where are those children now?
I killed them.
They started crying the first day I brought them in,
and I killed them without even realizing it.
Ever since then, I've killed all of
the children the day we brought them in.
But if anyone found out about that,
it would disrupt my organization.
So that's why I take the corpses of the children,
and to ensure that no evidence is left behind, I—
Enough!
I'm impressed.
You don't often find
such a textbook example of irredeemable scum,
you sham gentleman.
How dare you, girl?!
No fighting.
Now then, Galdo.
You have two options available to you.
The first is to try to kill everyone here
to keep them quiet.
The other is to run so far that no one
will be able to bring justice to you.
However, scum like you should always
meet the end they deserve,
reflecting upon their sins while being torn to shreds.
So I have another idea.
How about you play a Gift Game with us?
The continued existence of Fores Garo,
as well as our own No-Names, shall be on the line.
Y-You're going to play a game with Fores Garo?!
How did things get so serious so quickly?!
We were mad, so we picked a fight with him
without considering the consequences.
We regret nothing.
You two dummies!
But why did you allow it to come to this?
Sorry... I couldn't forgive what he did, either.
I... I understand how you feel, but...
Well, whatever.
Izayoi could beat Fores Garo all on his own, right?
I won't be participating.
What?
What's so hard to understand?
They're the ones who picked a fight with him.
It'd be downright rude of me to butt in.
Oh? So you understand.
Just do whatever you want, then.
So where are we going?
The game is tomorrow.
I was thinking of getting Thousand Eyes
to appraise your Gifts.
Thousand Eyes?
Yes! It's an extremely large trade community
that knows everything about the Little Garden,
from east to west, north to south, low and high.
Cherry blossoms?
It must be spring in this world.
It was midsummer where I came from.
It was fall where I was.
I summoned you all from different worlds.
Aside from your timelines,
there should be differences between
your histories and cultures, as well.
Parallel worlds, huh?
More specifically, it's the
"Parallel World Intersection Theory."
Hey, is that it?
Yes, that's Thousand Eyes...
It's been a while, Black Rabbit!
Black Rabbit just feels so right!
Is this it? Is this where it feels the best?
Sh-Shiroyasha?
Why did you knock me down here?
Actually, get away from me!
Who do you think you are, kicking a beautiful
young stranger about to fly into your arms?!
The name's Izayoi, kimono loli.
Nice to meet you.
How could I get all wet like this?
Hello there.
I am a senior official here at Thousand Eyes.
My name is Shiroyasha.
Our headquarters are located in
the four-digit region, gate #3345.
I know Black Rabbit from
some stuff that happened a while back
and I've been helping her out on occasion since then.
As you can see, I'm a very laid-back, beautiful girl.
What's a gate?
One of the openings that can be found in the walls
that divide the different layers of the Little Garden.
The smaller the number, the closer it is to the center.
And the stronger you are,
the closer you live to the center.
For example, our community
is close to the outermost edge,
a seven-digit gate number.
Any gate number of four digits or fewer,
like where I am,
is part of the Upper Levels.
You know that white serpent
you got the Water Tree from?
I'm the one who made it a god in the first place.
Oh?
So you're stronger than that serpent, then?
Of course.
I'm the Floor Master for the East Side.
We're by far the strongest community
in the four-digit region or outward on the East Side.
And I'm the strongest host there is.
The strongest host... Sounds fun.
Indeed. I'd like to face you.
W-Wait, you guys!
It's fine, Black Rabbit.
I've been short on playmates as of late.
What a coincidence.
I could say the same.
Play with us a little, "strongest host."
Very well.
But I'd like to check one thing first.
Are you looking for a challenge?
Or perhaps a duel?
What the?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
This is merely one of my game boards.
This is all just a game board?!
I am the Demon Lord of the White Night,
the spirit of the midnight sun
and arctic night, Shiroyasha.
I am one of the many Demon Lords
that inhabit the Little Garden.
A-A Demon Lord?
I ask you here.
Do you desire a challenge?
Or a fair duel?
Oh well. You got me, Shiroyasha.
Huh?
You showed me all of this.
I'll be quiet and let you test me.
Very well.
Shall we proceed to the game, then?
I'll have you take on one of those.
That's...
A griffin!
Indeed.
The king of not only birds, but beasts as well.
The mythical creature that represents the Gift Games.
I will test your power, wisdom,
and courage with this griffin.
The victory conditions are to ride on the griffin's back
and travel once around the lake.
Who will do it?
I will.
U-Um...
Nice to meet you. My name is Kasukabe You.
So she intends to talk to the griffin?
I could hardly retain my honor if I were unable
to shake off a young girl such as yourself.
What will you bet in exchange for my pride?
I will bet my life.
If I fall from you and still live,
you can have me for dinner.
Will that suffice?
Wh-What are you saying?!
Are you serious, Kasukabe?!
Step back, you two.
I'll be fine.
Very well.
Test that courage of yours
with the stride of a lion-eagle.
The lower body of a lion,
and the upper body of an eagle.
Just like my father said.
Are you ready?
Ready...
Go!
Wow! He's running through the air!
Will Kasukabe be okay?
Who knows?
But with that speed and the draft from the mountains,
the wind chill should put the temperature
a little below freezing.
She went behind the mountain!
The rest is up to her.
My father said that when you deal with a griffin,
you have to face him with all your might.
My father would always tell me fun stories
when I was in the hospital, and I'm sure he wouldn't...
If you allow your mind to wander,
you'll just end up as my meal.
I won't lose!
Over there!
You!
It seems her ability isn't just to talk to animals.
Given how violently the griffin is moving,
she must be experiencing
massive g-forces with each turn.
Any normal person would have
passed out a long time ago.
Father...
The gift I received from my father
so that I could walk outside
on my own two feet...
I won't lose!
I will win this game...
and we will be friends!
Interesting.
In that case, overcome this trial of mine!
There she is!
You!
She's starting to lose consciousness!
You can do it, Kasukabe!
Just a little bit further...
Well done!
You have won this match—
Kasukabe!
Little miss!
Calico Cat...
I knew it...
Your Gift is to take the abilities of other creatures
and make them your own.
I don't take them.
They're given to me as proof of our friendship.
Excellent work, friend.
I hope that when you use this gift I have left you,
you will remember our match and your victory.
Yes. I will treasure it.
You're really something.
By the way, were you born with that Gift of yours?
No, it was granted to me
by a wooden carving my father left me.
A wooden carving?
This.
A circular phylogenetic tree, huh?
Could I have you appraise them?
What? A-Appraise them?
That's totally out of my area, but...
Oh, wait.
Very well!
Let us celebrate your return in advance! Take these!
Are those... Gift Cards?
What's that? You mean a postcard?
A Christmas card?
A birthday card?
No! They have the capability to store your Gifts,
as well as name the Gifts that you have.
They're extremely valuable!
Then I guess mine's a rare case.
What?
"Unknown"?
The Gift Card, a Fragment of Laplace,
can't even read him...
Interesting.
However, I wonder how long you'll
keep that cocky expression on your face
after seeing what devastation
the Demon Lord left behind.
This is the destroyed land of the No-Names.
The soil's barren.
Hey, Black Rabbit, how many hundreds of years ago
was the Gift Game with the Demon Lord?
It was only three years ago.
That's quite strange.
From the looks of it, it seems like
almost two hundred years have passed.
It's not that strange when you consider
what the Demon Lords are capable of.
A Demon Lord, huh?
Sounds good. Real good.
Good, I say!
This looks like it'll be more fun than I thought.
Don't worry.
As promised, I gave you the Gift of the beast.
How you use it is up to you.
Now, what move will the new No-Names make?
So what's this "Parallel World
Intersection Theory," anyway?
It's when the lines from different timelines
and dimensions overlap, and...
Well, basically, if I were to
show you with Black Rabbit's ears...
Ouch ouch ouch!
H-Hey, what are you doing?!