Problems, challenges, obstacles too
My time's nearly up and I don't know what to do
Any place I could find a walkthrough?
Help me
Entered every cheat code I knew
Still stood no chance at all, what to do?
How many more twists can I go through?
Round in circles
My power and my skill level
Are all in single-digits, oh well
But what's this stat that's rising, pray tell?
It's just my stress?
None of my commands are working
None of the events are triggering
But he's getting tired of waiting
The final boss
Yes
If things stay the same
Oh yes
I won't reach the ending
I pay no heed to God's warnings
And set forth once more
To be continued?
Don't screw with me!
I can't wait until tomorrow
I'm heading straight to the finish line
Of course I'll continue
The fight starts here
Just watch me
I'll stick with it and have fun all the way
Let's play the game!