There's gotta be something fun going on.
I'm bored. Really bored.
If I could sell my boredom,
I'm pretty sure I could make a living.
C'mon, say something!
This dude's seriously crying.
Gross. Maybe a dip in the river'll wash him off.
Let's throw him in naked,
with his hands and feet tied up!
Look at him. He's practically pissed his pants!
What a little bitch. I can't believe it.
C'mon. Get naked and jump in the river.
I still think we should tie his hands up.
He won't die if he's got his legs.
S-Somebody... Anybody...
C'mon!
Hurry up and strip!
Hey! Let me in on the fun!
Want some more? I got plenty where that came from!
Oh shit, it's Sakamaki Izayoi!
Run for it!
S-Save me!
Pathetic!
You guys all bark and no bite?
That was boring.
Excuse me, Milady.
I've brought you a cold drin—
Hey, did anyone come in here while I was gone?
No.
Really?
Tell me the truth.
You're the only one with a key to this room, Milady.
No one else could have entered.
I suppose so.
That's enough.
You may leave.
Excuse me.
Someone's prepared a classic
locked-room mystery for me,
but instead of a murder, they've left me a letter.
How interesting.
This came from the sky?
Th-This is unbelievable.
They just tossed us into the sky without any warning.
We're lucky we didn't crash
into the ground and break our necks.
Yeah, seriously.
We were this close to it being game over.
So, who are you guys?
I'd like to ask you the same,
Mr. Mean-Looking Student.
Just to make sure,
you guys got that weird letter too?
Yes, but please refrain
from addressing me in that manner.
My name is Kudou Asuka.
Be sure to remember it.
And who might you be, cat girl?
Kasukabe You. It was the same for me.
I see. Nice to meet you, Miss Kasukabe.
And you, the unrefined,
dangerous-looking one, would be?
I have to thank you for that wonderfully
antagonistic introduction of yours.
As you can see, I'm unrefined, dangerous,
and the name's Sakamaki Izayoi.
I'm also crude, vicious, and hedonistic,
and well past the point of redemption.
I'd recommend reading all
the warning labels beforehand
so that you'll understand how best
to conduct yourself around me, Milady.
I'll think about it if you properly
document all those warning labels.
Seriously?
I'll write something up a bit later,
so you better be ready.
Oh my, these three all have
the most outrageous personalities.
But that's exactly why they're...
Okay, so someone brought us here,
but where the hell are they?
Good question.
Well, that's my cue.
Great.
How about we ask the person hiding over there?
Oh, you noticed her too?
Of course. I never lose at hide and seek.
You noticed too, right?
From downwind, I can tell they're there,
even if I don't want to.
You're pretty interesting.
I totally missed my chance to make an entrance.
Hey, you know we know you're there, right?
Just come out already.
G-Guess I have no choice.
Oh my, please don't glare at me like th—
If you're not gonna come out on your own, fine.
What is that?
Cosplay?
N-No, this isn't cosplay...
Birds, restrain her at once.
W-Wait a second!
Ouch, that hurt...
Who is this?
A bunny girl?
P-Please calm down, everyone!
W-Wait a second!
What on Earth are you trying to accomplish
by pulling off Black Rabbit's beautiful ears
the moment you meet her!?
It sates my curiosity.
That doesn't mean you can just do as you please!
So these bunny ears are real, then?
Let me feel.
W-Wait! My poor rabbit ears are...
I... I can't believe this.
This must be what it's like
to teach a class full of unruly children.
Just hurry up and talk.
Right.
Welcome to the world of Little Garden!
Little Garden?
Yes!
We are willing to offer the three of you
a chance to participate in the Gift Games.
That's why we called you here.
The Gift Games?
You might have realized already,
but the three of you are not normal humans.
The special powers that you possess
are Gifts that were granted to you
by various war gods, demons, spirits, and stars.
In other words, blessings.
The Gift Games are competitive contests
that make use of those blessings
and even allow you to place wagers with them.
The Little Garden is one big stage
that was created for this purpose.
Do we have to wager our own abilities to play?
Not necessarily.
There are various other chips you may wager.
Gifts, money, land, resources, prestige, and people.
The higher the value of the chips you place,
the greater the rewards you can win.
However, in order to receive a reward,
you must clear the conditions set by the host
and win the game.
Question.
Go ahead.
What's a host?
They are the people who preside over
the Gift Games and administer them.
Can anyone become one?
As long as you can prepare a prize.
That's why you can see games hosted by anyone
from war gods to shopping district merchants.
The games range from being treacherous,
difficult, and life-threatening,
to simple lotteries.
There are all kinds!
However, I'm sure much of
my explanation flew over your heads.
So how about we play a simple game right now?
What?
There are communities of sorts in this world.
Communities, collectives, societies.
Residents of this world must
be part of a given community.
Or rather, you could say that it's
difficult to live without being part of one.
I wouldn't mind letting you join
the community that I'm part of,
but having people around who can't
win Gift Games would be a problem.
Indeed, quite a serious problem.
You'd drag us down, bringing nothing but trouble.
You'd hold everyone back.
Are you trying to test us?
Wait a second! We haven't even said anything!
If you're not up to it,
you can always refuse.
What am I saying?
If they get angry now and head back home,
I'm going to be in a lot of trouble.
That's quite an interesting challenge of yours.
I'm glad you liked it.
So what are the rules of this game?
We'll use these cards.
Your goal is to pick face cards
from the fifty-two cards you see here,
but you only get one chance,
and each person can only pick one card.
Can we use any method we wish?
As long as it doesn't conflict with the rules.
By the way, I happen to have
the ability of "Judge Master."
You can't break the rules when I'm around.
My eyes and ears are connected
to the Little Garden's central network.
What are the chips? Are we wagering our Gifts?
You've all just arrived at the Little Garden,
so we'll play without chips this time.
If I had to say, I guess you'd be
putting your pride on the line?
What if we win?
Let's see...
In that case, as a servant of a god,
I'll do any one thing that you ask of me.
Oh? Anything, you say?
Um... Anything sexual is off-limits!
Just messing with you.
So, what are we gonna do?
Do you have to ask?
Right. Let's do it.
Yeah.
Game established!
What's that?
A Geas Roll.
A contract of sorts pertaining to the game.
The rules of the game,
as well as the conditions for winning, are written here.
Okay, got it.
But beforehand, let us take a look at those cards.
Sure, I don't mind.
Okay, we're starting the game!
Who's going first?
Guess I'll volunteer.
Thanks for that wonderfully intimidating speech earlier.
N-No problem.
I'll take this one!
Wa—
Then, I'll take this one.
I'll take this one.
W-Wait just a second!
That wasn't...
We're not breaking any rules.
We chose face cards from the cards on the table.
One card per person.
Am I wrong?
Y-You aren't, but...
The Little Garden's central net
has determined that your method was valid.
Asuka and You have met the victory conditions.
We did it.
B-But, you haven't won yet, Izayoi!
Hey, just who do you think I am?
H-How did you...
I memorized them.
I memorized the position of every single card.
Next to this one's the nine of diamonds.
This is the two of clubs. The jack of spades.
You're pretty good.
Though it's a shame we didn't get to use
any of the tricks we had up our sleeves.
Sorry about that.
Hey, Black Rabbit.
Y-Yes?
How about you do something
for me right here and now?
I-I said nothing sexual!
That sounds fun in its own right,
but there's only one thing I want to ask of you.
Wh-What is it?
Is this world fun?
Yes!
The Gift Games are heavenly
and demonic games in which only
those who have surpassed
normal humans can participate.
I'll personally guarantee that the Little Garden
is far more interesting than the outside world!
Jin!
Lily!
Thanks, guys.
Is Black Rabbit still not back?
Yeah.
I know you're going through
a lot as leader, but keep it up.
Master Jin, I've brought new friends!
Welcome back, Black Rabbit.
Are those two women the ones?
Yes, these three here are—
Huh? Where's the third?
Izayoi said he was going to check out
the edge of the world real quick and took off.
Why didn't you stop him?!
He told us not to stop him.
Why didn't you tell me?!
He said, "Don't tell Black Rabbit."
You're lying. You've got to be lying.
You two just didn't want to bother with it, did you?
Yeah.
B-Black Rabbit, the edge of the world is...
I know.
Master Jin, please lead them the rest of the way.
I will capture our problem child!
You've insulted me, an aristocrat of the Little Garden!
I'll make you wish you were never born!
Rabbits can hop around pretty fast here in Little Garden.
The rabbits are the servants
of the founder of the Little Garden.
Anyway, come this way.
I'll show you into the Little Garden.
This is...
The Little Garden...
I thought we were entering a covered area,
but I can see the sun.
The coverings over the Little Garden
are invisible from the inside.
They were set up to protect races
that cannot be directly exposed to the sun.
So are there vampires living here or something?
Huh? Yes, there are.
I see.
There are a wide variety of races living here.
Gods, demons, spirits, animal-human hybrids,
and humans themselves.
There are lots of agricultural districts
here in the East Side,
so everything's quite peaceful.
I'm sure you're still itching
to move around since you've just arrived.
How about we grab a bite and go over the details?
Come on. How far could he have gone?
Certain gods use this area as their game territory.
If he gets tricked by them
and roped into playing one of their games...
He couldn't have...
Oh, are you Black Rabbit?
What happened to your hair color?
How far do you think you've gone?!
To the edge of the world, I think.
Well, don't get so upset.
I was worried you might have
challenged a god to a Gift Game!
Anyway, since you're fine, let's head ba—
I did challenge one.
Huh?
A god to a Gift Game.
What?
No... The trial isn't over yet, kid!
A water god!
How did you make him so mad?!
He told me arrogantly to pick a game,
so I told him to see if he could
give me a run for my money.
Izayoi...
Don't be so conceited, human.
Do you think you can defeat me so easily?
Izayoi! Get back!
What are you going on about?
You're the one who needs to get back, Black Rabbit.
I picked this fight, and he wants to finish it.
You know, you've got guts.
If you can take this blow, I'll give you the win.
You've got to be kidding.
A fight isn't won once a victor is decided,
it's won when someone loses.
That's the last dumb thing
that'll ever come out of your mouth!
Izayoi!
Little too soon for that!
No way!
That can't be!
You know, you were pretty good.
A human beat a god?
This can't be...
I sure am getting wet a lot today.
No, that's why he's... If I have his power...
I'll have two black teas and one green.
Also...
Okay, that'll be three teas and some cat food.
You can understand what Calico Cat says?
Of course I can. I'm of the cat persuasion.
Oh, you're such a smooth talker!
The Little Garden is amazing.
There are people other than me
who can understand Calico Cat's words.
W-Wait, you can talk with cats?
Yeah.
Sparrows, bush warblers, cuckoos...
I've talked to penguins in the aquarium, as well.
I've even made friends with dolphins.
That's quite a useful Gift.
Indeed.
You have a wonderful ability, Kasukabe.
I'm a little envious.
But, Kudou, you...
You can call me Asuka.
Nice to be here with you, Kasukabe.
But you have the same power, Asuka.
Huh?
You were talking to the birds in the forest.
Oh, that? That was different.
My power is...
Well, if it isn't the leader
of the weakest community on the East Side,
Jin of the No-Names.
Galdo...
Who might you be?
Hey there, ladies.
I'm the leader of the Fores Garo community,
Galdo Gasper.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Look at this!
We won this big Water Tree sapling!
Now that we have this, we won't have
to buy water from the other communities!
You've really helped everyone out!
That so?
Mind if I ask you something
while you're in a good mood?
Go ahead!
Black Rabbit, you've been hiding something
deal-breaking this whole time, haven't you?
Answer me.
Why did you need to call us here?
What is a Little Garden aristocrat, anyway?
That title is held by the rabbits,
who possess the great power of judging Gift Games.
What happens if you break the rules in front of them?
You explode.
You explode?
In a great flash!